

# Rodhi Faisal Mufid

github.com/themufid

in linkedin.com/in/rodhifaisalmufid/

twitter.com/faisalmufidd/

Summary

I have experience in both Frontend and Backend. I have expertise in creating engaging social media content, writing informative articles, and building websites with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Vue.js, Django API, and WordPress. I have a passion to keep learning and developing myself, especially in writing and coding.

I have an interest in writing coding. I want to learn more about it and am ambitious to change the world with technology.

#### Education

### Institut Informatika dan Bisnis Darmajaya

Bachelor of Informatics Engineering Agustus 2019 – Agustus 2023 **IPK 3.74** 

### Skill

Digital Marketing • HTML • CSS • Javascript • Vue.is • Diango • Python • Copywriting • Microsoft Office • Content Writing • Social Media Admin • Content Creation

### **Tools**

 Canva (Design) • Microsoft Office (Content Planning) • Kinemaster (Reels Editing) • Visual Studio Code (Coding Web) • Wordpress • Github • Linux • Jupyter • Figma (UI Design) • Adobe XD

# **Experience**

#### Founder

Muana Media Teknologi

Feb 2023 - Present (5 months)

- 1. Handle social media instagram, linkedin, and website.
- 2. Creating new events and programs
- 3. Creating brand names
- 4. Creating new copywriting and content
- 5. Creating a content strategy
- 6. Promoting the program that has been created

# Content Writer

Leanomad

May 2021 - Apr 2023 (2 years)

Traveling is my passion, sharing knowledge and learning from each other is what I love.

### Software Engineer

PT. Stechog Robotika Indonesia

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022 (5 months)

1. Create a portfolio website using HTML, CSS + Tailwind, Bootstrap, Javascript

- 2. Create a simple design component using Figma
- 3. Create a project frontend is Dasboard with Vue.js 3 (Pinia, Axios, Plugin integration, and Deployment)
- 4. Create a four operator calculator using Javascript, run with Node.is, and save at modul fs
- 5. Create API using framework Express.js, ORM Prisma, and Database MySQL
- 6. Directing a front-end team, and dividing tasks for the process of working on the final project

### Digital Marketing

Tunas Honda

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022 (4 months)



### 🚷 Teacher Assistant Kampus Mengajar

Kementerian Pendidikan dan Kebudayaan (Ministry of Education and Culture Republic of Indonesia)

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021 (5 months)

- Provide administrative data entry assistance at school
- Directly involved in the implementation of literacy, numeracy, and technology adaptation at junior high
- Create a website for classroom learning in English subjects with HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Teacher assistance in completing administrative, and classroom learning

## Distributor

PT. MMBC Tour & Travel

Aug 2020 - Aug 2021 (1 year 1 month)

Become a partner of PT. MMBC Tour & Travel with the name of "Mufid Digital Store". Promoting, and selling product through social media

# Social Media Officer | Scholars Sumatera

Scholars Official

Apr 2020 - Mar 2021 (1 year)

Jobdesk

- Create and manage social media Instagram from '@Scholars Sumatera' (Reply to messages, comments, and content uploads)
- Make a copywriting for content feed and story instagram
- Managing human resources in whatsapp groups, organizing, and collaborating on creating events
- Interviewing volunteers who want to join the community and social media officer division

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rodhifaisalmufid/details/certifications/